<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Mitra</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_send_mail_screen">SendMailScreen</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="yesno">
        <item>Yes</item>
        <item>No</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="vas_benefits">
        <item>a) Health Problems solved</item>
        <item>b) Productivity improved</item>
        <item>c) Health Expendityre avoided</item>
        <item>d) Family members helped</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="caste_options">
        <item>a) General Category</item>
        <item>b) Backward Caste / Community</item>
        <item>c) Schedule Cast</item>
        <item>d) Schedule Tribe</item>
        <item>e) Others</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="good_not_good">
        <item>Good</item>
        <item>Not Good</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sub_4">
        <item>Unclean public markets selling food</item>
        <item>Fertilizers and pesticides leaking into water sources</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="aboutTitle">About</string>
    <string name="aboutString">
<![CDATA[Healthizen is a mobile application that connects the concerned active 
            citizen of Bangalore City directly to the Health Department by providing an 
            easy channel to bring important issues regarding community health and sanitation 
            to the department.<br /><br />
            This simple tool that is Healthizen allows the people to take authority and 
            help the government in making the city cleaner, healthier and 
            safer for the people who call it home. The population works as one: 
            citizens are the eyes, and the concerned authorities the hands and legs 
            that perform the tasks. To be successful, one needs the other.<br /><br />
            The app interfaces with the camera present in smart phones and tablets, 
            and allows them to send pictures of the issue that they want to flag to the 
            concerned authorities.We prefer to call the issues that you point out as 
            ‘flags’ rather than complaints. This isn’t a complaint anymore.<br /><br />
             You are an active member of society doing your part in making the city a 
             cleaner place.<br /><br />
			Though we would like to, we cannot guarantee that the flags are addressed. 
			What we can guarantee, is that the flags are received and read by the concerned 
			authorities and the Healthizen team has mechanisms in place for this. 
			Multiple flags that haven’t been addressed will show us that a pressing matter 
			has not been taken care of. This will allow those in power to put 
			pressure on the concerned authorities to take the necessary steps.<br /><br />
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="flagBtnLabel">Flag</string>
    <string name="aboutBtnLabel">About</string>
    <string name="faqsBtnLabel">FAQs</string>
    <string name="reviewBtnLabel">Review</string>
    <string name="faqTitle">FAQs</string>
    <string name="faqString">
<![CDATA[Read the “About Healthizen” tab to learn what the app does, and how to use it. <br /><br />

<font color="red"> <b> 1. How is my flag going to help? <br /></b> </font>
By sending a flag using Healthizen, you make the authorities aware of a problem 
that they could have missed out on. When they are made aware of the problem, they 
will be able to correct it. And it is with your help that they were able to do so. 
A simple flag on your part could do something big like help stop a malaria outbreak,
 or even just make your neighborhood cleaner. <br />
<font color="red"> <b>2. Who will my flag reach? <br /> </b> </font>
Our internal routing mechanism will ensure that your flag will reached the concerned 
authority in the specified area, so that appropriate action can be taken. <br />
<font color="red"> <b>3. Will the concerned authority who receives my flag be answerable? <br /></b></font>
We cannot force the authorities to act. But like us, they too want to see a cleaner and safer Bangalore.
 We can guarantee that the issue you point out reaches the eyes of people who can correct it. <br />
<font color="red"> <b> 4. Where can I check the status of my flag? <br /> </b></font>
We will be setting up a website which lists all flags and their statuses. You can check the status of your flag on this site.<br />
<font color="red"><b>5. If I’m unsure of the category of my flag, what do I do? <br /></b></font>
No need to worry! Mark the category of the flag as others, and add a detailed comment, and we 
shall appropriately route it to the concerned department.<br />
<font color="red"><b>6. Why aren’t anonymous flags allowed? <br /></b></font>
If we receive a complaint, we must be able to see who sent it, so that we can contact the person for further details of required. <br />
<font color="red"><b>7. Will Healthizen be releasing in non-android versions? <br /></b></font>
Yes, Healthizen will release on iOS and Windows Phone as well.<br />
<font color="red"><b>8. What can I write in comments? <br /></b></font>
The comments section is for any subjective information that you may want to provide. 
It could be extra information that we can’t see from the picture, such as that there are 
stray dogs all around the garbage pile, or it could even be a landmark so that we can find 
the site of your flag easily. <br />
<font color="red"><b>Why is the app called ‘Healthizen’? <br /></b></font>
Healthizen is a portmanteau of the words ‘Health’ and ‘Citizen’ – a nod to public 
engagement in governance. A concerned citizen takes the matter of public health into his 
own hands and helps authorities track down issues in our city. <br />
            ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="bgColorPrimary">#47C1D1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form_page_1">Form_page_1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form_page1">FormPage1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form_page2">FormPage2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form_page3">FormPage3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form_page4">FormPage4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form_page5">FormPage5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form_page6">FormPage6</string>

</resources>